

Marcin Grzmil

front-end developer

About

Fine design and bringing it into life is what I am passionate about. That is why I decided to change the course of my career to web development. With the background in engineering I am lookinng to get first commercial experience as a frontend developer.

Skills

- Semantic HTML + CSS/SASS
- javascript, typescript
- rest api, microservices
- next
- react
- state mangaement mobx, redux
- routing
- unit-testing jest, pupeteer
- git, gitlab ci/cd
- mobile-first, browserstack
- webpack, yarn
- linux, bash
- logs jaeger, kibana, grafana
- problem solving
- good communication skills
- English B2/C1

Contact adress

Lelewela 3/36 80-452 Gdańsk

phone

+48 511-592-770

email

marcin.grzmil@hotmail.com

linkedin

linkedin.com/in/marcin-grzmil

github

github.com/g-marcin

blog

g-marcinjournal.blogspot.com

Experience

junior front-end developer

wakacje.pl Aug 2023 - present

front-end intern

sii

Apr 2023 - Jul 2023

- development and maintenance of ecommerce service
- Working using version control systems and SCRUM and agile
- team cooperation code-review, maintaining clear code, refactoring code.
- HTML and CSS layouts including responsive web design and SEO
- Working using version control systems and SCRUM and agile
- Regular code-review, maintaining clear code, refactoring code.

Education

Gdynia Maritime University

Engineer degree Sep 2014 - Feb 2019

Engineer of Nautical Science

 Learned in-depth how to manage resources during navigational watch: use navigational instruments, correct navigational charts, perform a chartwork and doct with part documents. Solvi

Pobierz PDF

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r.